Guide to the Homo Xtra (HX) records, circa 1991-2009.
Homo Xtra (HX) records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Homo Xtra (HX) records, circa 1991-2009.
7840
Matthew Bank
4.2 cubic feet.
Printed materials, media, manuscripts.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Organizational files from the co-publisher Matthew Blank.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
A weekly gay entertainment guide for New York City, 1991 to July 10, 2009, HX, titled Homo Xtra for a while, was available for free in bars and other locations, concentrated in the West Village and Chelsea and, during the summer, in the Pines and Cherry Grove. Its slogan was: "The totally biased, politically incorrect party paper".
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Organizational files from the co-publisher Matthew Blank.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bank, Matthew
Subjects:
Gay men -- New York; Gay men -- Social life and customs
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Periodicals cataloged separately as part of the Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- 11 t-shirts, 1994-1998 (Box 1)
- Fashion, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Books, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Sam Hamadah photographs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Clue 11 - Mature BSB Fanclub
- B. Campbell, Dukakis, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Aaron Cobbett, 1996-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Feature log cabin, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- South Africa, 2001-01 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Travel, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Music, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Film, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Empire, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Rufus, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Resources, 2000-12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Sigur Ros, 1999-12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Miami fashion creds, 2002-05 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Cowboy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Blue dot design, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Empire invoices, Expression (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Invoices, 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Misc. gay porn material, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Fashion credits, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous fashion, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Products, techno-gadgets, clue, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous communications, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Apple powerbook, 2001-01 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Mini cooper, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- San Francisco MoMA Nike, 2000-10-31 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Diesel, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- New York fashion cares, 2001-04 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- The Flinstones in Viva Rock Vegas, 2000-03 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Writer contracts, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Empire spread proofs, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Empire layout notes, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Model release forms, 2002 Spring (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Empire fall model, photographer release, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Prices and descriptions, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Gay life exposition, 2000-09-09 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Paragraph 175, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Boys Life 3, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Empire 7, add, ID #4023, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Empire 7, add, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Empire 7, add, ID #3916, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Photos/slides, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Adds/publicity, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Clues, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Art, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Fall fashion credits, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- "Random shit" (film art), 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Summer clue photo shoots credits, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Winter credits, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Preppy fashion credits, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Proofs 1a and 1b, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Proofs 2a and 2b, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Proofs 3a and 3b, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Old photos not for press, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Michael C. Hall, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Summer skin, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Keenan Duffty, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Monica, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Jean Paul Gaultier, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Spring outlines, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Design/home, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Clue 9, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Books, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Guillero Diaz, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Goodman Charlton, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Fashion clue, Fall 2001 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Jack Pierson/Whitney Museum of American Art biennial, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- B.D.B music, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Art clue, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Clues and products search, Winter 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Aiden Shaw, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Polari, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Contributors, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Proofs, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Vieques write-ups, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Photography invoices, 2000-08-24 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Times of Harvey Milk press material, 2000-08-18 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Clue fashion, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Stephen Petronio Company press material, 2000-06-2000-07 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Match print layout, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Hammacher Schlemmer advertising materials, 2000-11 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Holiday gift ideas, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Braun Synchro system advertising material, 2001-07-13 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Ariel group advertising material, 2001-10 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Advertising materials, Fall 2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Stan Winston press material, 2001-09 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Scott Seomin press material, 2001-03-30 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 1888petoq11.org press material, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Home and real estate press material, 2001-05-2001-09 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Judy Garland book press material, 2002-07 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Double Xxposure press material, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Champagne Duval-Leroy press material, 2001-09 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Jason Lee press material, 2002-05-06 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Holiday gift guides, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Jaguar advertising material, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Kyocera phone advertising material, 2001-04 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- John Frieda advertising material, 2002-01 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Tech advertising material, 2001-03-2001-08 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Assorted advertising material, 2001-06-2001-09 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Fashion credits, 2002-01-2002-02 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- The Trip credits, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Fashion credits, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Empire 4 invoices, 2000-11-2000-12 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Empire 5 invoices, 2001-01-2001-02 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Empire 6 invoices, 2001-04-2001-05 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Empire 8 invoices, 2001-09-2001-12 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Empire 9 invoices, 2002-03-2002-10 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Andrew Mackenzie, 2002-01-08 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Laramie, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Gavin Benjamin, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- The Cockettes, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Film spring, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Clue beauty, Spring 2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Misc. publications, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Gay games VII brochure, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- HX annual awards, 1994-1998 (Box 6)
- HX sponsored event publications (GLAMA, Pride Rally, Gay Rites, Wigstock, Not Wig), 1993-1996 (Box 6)
- Gay Life/Erotic Exposition programs, 2000-2006 (Box 6)
- The Pines phone book and Cherry Grove phone book, 1998-2004 (Box 6)
- Shooting Dirty, DVD-2615 (Box 6)
  1 DVD
- Digitized art/adds used in various issues of HX, CD-3818-3843
  26 CDs
- Digitized art/adds used in various issues of HX, ZD-71-79
  9 zip disks
- Vieques article, FD-671
  1 floppy disk